updato.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | Updato

See [how Google uses data when you use their partners’ sites or apps](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

Updato (“Updato”) operates Updato.com and may operate other websites. It is Updato’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, Updato collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Updato’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Updato’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Updato may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Updato also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Updato.com blogs/sites. Updato only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to Updato’s websites choose to interact with Updato in ways that require Updato to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Updato gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at Updato.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Updato are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Updato collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Updato. Updato does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply or revoke personally-identifying information by emailing team@updato.com, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
Updato may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Updato may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Updato does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
Updato discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Updato’s behalf or to provide services available at Updato’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Updato’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Updato will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Updato discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Updato believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Updato, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Updato website and have supplied your email address, Updato may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Updato and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Updato takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Updato uses cookies to help Updato identify and track visitors, their usage of Updato website, and their website access preferences. Updato visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Updato’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Updato’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**  
If Updato, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Updato goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Updato may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Updato and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Your IDFA/Advertising Identifier**  
We also collect where provided your devices IDFA/Advertising Identifer which is an annonymous ID provided by your operating system. We may pass this anonymised data to a third party partner for purposes of providing accurate and relevant advertising across various operating systems and devices and to analyse the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. Details of how to opt out of IDFA/AAID data sharing can be found on your mobile device operating settings.

**X. THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS – YOUR AD CHOICES**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Websites and/or use the Mobile Apps. These companies may use information about your visits to any of the Websites and other websites and the Mobile App(s) and other mobile applications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You have the ability to opt out of the use of your information for purposes of online third-party advertising. If you would like more information about your choices, visit aboutads.info. You may have the ability to manage tracking and ad preferences on your mobile device from your devices settings. We do not respond to Web browser “do not track” signals or other similar mechanisms.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Updato may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Updato’s sole discretion. Updato encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Updato.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
